messageme.com 2014-02-09

# MessageMe | Fun, FREE, messaging :)

We at **_LittleInc Labs, Inc._** (“Company,” “we,” “us,” “our”) know that our users (“you,” “your”) care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. **By visiting or using the Website or Services in any manner, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby consent that we will collect, use, and share your information in the following ways.** Any capitalized terms used herein without definition shall have the meaning given to them in the Company Terms of Use.

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that we gather when you are accessing or using our Service. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined in our Terms of Use). If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@messageme.com](mailto:support@messageme.com).

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We only use this Personal Information to provide and personalize and improve our services, to allow our users to set up a user account and profile, to contact users, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to analyze how users utilize the Service, and as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. No Personal Information, including any communication privately shared by you via the Service to another user or a group of users selected by you, will be shared by us with any third parties, except as described in this Section and in Section III below. We collect the following types of information:

## A. Information You Provide to Us:

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. For example, we collect Personal Information such as your name, email address, phone number, browser information, and third-party account credentials (for example, your log-in credentials for Facebook or other third party sites). If you provide your third-party account credentials to us, some content and/or information in those accounts (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Service is covered by this Privacy Policy. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some of our features. We may share aggregated, anonymized data based on usage of our Service to our partners.

## B. Information Collected Automatically:

  * Whenever you interact with our Service, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when pages in our Service are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our Service’s features. Our advertising partners may also transmit cookies to your computer or device, when you click on ads that appear on the Service. Also, if you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.
  * When we collect usage information (such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to the Service), we only use this data in aggregated, anonymized form, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. For example, this aggregate data tells us how often users use parts of the Service, so that we can make the Service appealing to as many users as possible. We may also provide this aggregate information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Service, so that they, too, can provide you with an optimal experience. We never disclose aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

## C. E-mail and Other Communications:

We may contact you, by email or other means to communicate information about the Service. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by contacting us a [support@messageme.com](mailto:support@messageme.com). Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Service, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We do not share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form with third parties except as described below.

**A. Agents:** We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. 

**B. User Profiles and Submissions:** Certain user profile information, including without limitation a user’s name, and any video or image content that such user has uploaded to the Service, may be displayed to other users to facilitate user interaction within the Service or address your request for Company’s services. Your account privacy settings allow you to limit the other users who can see the Personal Information in your user profile and/or what information in your user profile is visible to others. Any content you upload to your public user profile, along with any Personal Information or content that you voluntarily disclose online in a manner other users can view (in messages, for example) becomes available to those with whom you share it, and can be collected and used by those users. Your user name may also be displayed to other users if and when you send messages or comments or upload images or videos through the Service and other users can contact you through messages and comments. Additionally, if you sign into the Service through a third party social networking site or service, your list of “friends” from that site or service may be automatically imported to the Service, and such “friends,” if they are also registered users of the Service, may be able to access certain non-public information you have entered in your Service user profile. Again, we do not control the policies and practices of any other third party site or service.

**C. Business Transfers:** We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or substantially all of our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party. 

**D. Protection of Company and Others:** We reserve the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information that we reasonably believe is necessary to comply with law or court order; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**E. With Your Consent:** Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties in personally identifiable form, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via a third party site or service, you may have additional or different sign-on protections via that third party site or service. You must prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password and/or other sign-on mechanism appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We endeavor to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

The Service may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site’s privacy policy.

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you’ve provided to us:

  * name and password
  * email address
  * location
  * user profile information, including images and videos you have uploaded to the site

**The information you can view, update, and delete may change as the Service changes. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at[support@messageme.com](mailto:support@messageme.com). Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of Personal Information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to: [support@messageme.com](mailto:support@messageme.com).**

  * You can always opt not to disclose information to use, but keep in mind some information may be needed to register with us or to take advantage of some of our special features.
  * You may be able to add, update, or delete information as explained in Section V above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your account by sending a written request to [support@messageme.com](mailto:support@messageme.com). Please note that some information may remain in our records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Service or sending you an email. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Service after such changes have been first posted.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to [support@messageme.com](mailto:support@messageme.com), and we will try to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: December 4, 2012
